Guide to the Tony Judt Papers MC 233
New York University Archives
- Series V: Lectures/Conferences/Addresses
  - Remarque Lecture: "What is Living and What is Dead in Social Democracy?" new quotes and epigraphs, general notes and thoughts, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Remarque Lecture: "What is Living and What is Dead in Social Democracy?" outline, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Remarque Lecture: "What is Living and What is Dead in Social Democracy?" outline, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Remarque Lecture: "What is Living and What is Dead in Social Democracy?" outline, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Remarque Lecture: "What is Living and What is Dead in Social Democracy?" transcript for NYR publication, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Remarque Lecture: "What is Living and What is Dead in Social Democracy?" Q&A transcript, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Remarque Lecture: "What is Living and What is Dead in Social Democracy?" adapted transcript, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Remarque Lecture: "What is Living and What is Dead in Social Democracy?" correspondence, articles (post-lecture), 2009 (Box 22, Folder 54)
- Series VI: Administrative Files (INTERNAL ONLY, NOT A DUPLICATE)
  Conditions Governing Access
  This material is temporarily restricted, allow access as 20-year period allows. However, some folders in this series will remain restricted regardless.
  The files in this series mostly come from the Remarque Institute's offices, with some of Judt's other administrative files dispersed throughout. The Remarque files are comprised of correspondence and material related to the Institute's programming. The material spans 1993 to 2009.
  - Center for European Studies Annual Report, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - College Work Study, 1996-1998 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Gen Ed - MAP, 2007-2008 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Gen Ed - MAP, 2007-2008 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Gen Ed - MAP, 2007-2008 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Gen Ed - MAP, 2008, undated (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Institute of French Studies, 1996-1999 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Institute of French Studies, 1996-1999 (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - Max Weber Chair, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Max Weber Chair, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - NEH ERC, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - NEH Financial, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - NEH Reports, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - NYU Rental Office Memos, 1994-2001 (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - NYU Rental Office Memos, 1994-2001 (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - NYU Rental Office Memos, 1994-2001 (Box 22, Folder 70)
  - Remarque Institute admin. misc., undated (Box 22, Folder 71)
  - Remarque Institute admin. misc., 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 72)
  - Remarque Institute admin. misc., 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 73)
  - Remarque Institute admin. misc., 2002 (Box 22, Folder 74)
  - Remarque Institute brochures, undated (Box 22, Folder 75)
  - Remarque Institute - Amos Elon Memorial, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 76)
  - Remarque Institute Forum packet "Faith and the State", 2004 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Remarque Institute Forum packet "The Future of the West", 2003 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Remarque Institute Forum packet "Responsibility and Its Discontents", 2001 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Remarque Institute staffing, 1994-1997 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Remarque Institute workshop packet "Birth of a Refugee Nation", 2001 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Remarque Lecture - Robert Alter, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Remarque Lecture - Robert Alter, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Remarque Lecture - Mark Danner, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Remarque Lecture - Mark Danner, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Remarque Lecture - Saul Friedländer, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Remarque Lecture - Saul Friedländer, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Remarque Lecture - Saul Friedländer, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Remarque Lecture - Saul Friedländer, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Remarque Lecture - Saul Friedländer, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Remarque Lecture - Saul Friedländer, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Remarque Lecture - Saul Friedländer, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Remarque Lecture - Saul Friedländer, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Remarque Lecture - David Halberstam, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Remarque Lecture - David Halberstam, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Remarque Lecture - Michael Ignatieff, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Remarque Lecture - Michael Ignatieff, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Remarque Lecture - Michael Ignatieff, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Remarque Lecture - Michael Ignatieff, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Remarque Lecture - Michael Ignatieff, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Remarque Lecture - Michael Ignatieff, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Remarque Lecture - Michael Ignatieff, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Remarque Lecture - Tony Judt, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Remarque Lecture - Martha Nussbaum, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Remarque Lecture - Martha Nussbaum, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Remarque Lecture - Martha Nussbaum, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Remarque Lecture - Martha Nussbaum, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Remarque Lecture - Martha Nussbaum, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Remarque Lecture - Anne-Marie Slaughter, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Remarque Lecture - Anne-Marie Slaughter, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Jack Tchen tenure, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Jack Tchen tenure, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Series VI: Administrative Files
  Administrative records are closed for 20 years after their date of creation.
  Contact the University Archives for details.
- Series VII: Correspondence
  Subseries A is organized alphabetically by given and created folder titles.
  Subseries B is organized alphabetically by correspondent.
  Subseries A: Chronological, Misc. contains correspondence from throughout the collection. There was some pre-existing order to the material, but much of it was scattered and brought together into one series.
  Subseries B: By Correspondent was a pre-existing grouping of files, titled "Colleagues." Original order was maintained here and the material was placed within this series.
  - Subseries A: Chronological, Misc.
    - Accepted Invitations, 1997-2001 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Accepted Invitations, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Accepted Invitations, 2004-2005 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Accepted Invitations, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Accepted Invitations, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Accepted Invitations, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Accepted Invitations, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - re: articles, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - re: articles, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - re: articles, 2001-2007 (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - re: articles, 2000-2007 (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - John Bentley, Data, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - children's letters, replies, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - chronological, Dec. 2002-Jan. 2003, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - chronological, Jan.-April 2004 (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - chronological, May-Dec. 2004, 2004-2005 (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - chronological, July-Sept. 2005 (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - chronological, Jan. 2006 (Box 23, Folder 54)
    - chronological, March-June 2006 (Box 23, Folder 55)
    - chronological, Aug.-Sept. 2006 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - chronological, Oct. 2006 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - chronological, Nov. 2006 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - chronological, Dec. 2006-Feb. 2007, 2006-2007 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - chronological, March 2007 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - chronological, April 2007 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - chronological, May-June 2007 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - chronological, July-Sept. 2007 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - chronological, Sept. 2007 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - chronological, Sept.-Nov. 2007 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - chronological, Dec. 2007 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - chronological, Jan.-Feb. 2008 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - chronological, March-April 2008 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - chronological, May 2008 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - chronological, June 2008 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - chronological, July-Oct. 2008 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - crackpots, undated, 2006-2010 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Declined Invitations, 2004-2005 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Declined Invitations, 2005-2006 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Declined Invitations, 2006 January-February (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Declined Invitations, 2006 February-May (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Declined Invitations, 2006 June-July (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Declined Invitations, 2006 August-September (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Declined Invitations, 2006 October-December (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Declined Invitations, 2007 January-March (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Declined Invitations, 2007 April (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Declined Invitations, 2007 May-September (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Declined Invitations, 2007 September (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Declined Invitations, 2007 October-2008 February (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Declined Invitations, 2008 March-May (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Declined Invitations, 2008 July-November (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Declined Invitations - Riverdale, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Farrar, Straus and Giroux, 1996-1998 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - re: foreign articles, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - re: foreign articles, 1997-2001 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - HarperCollins, 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Invitations - Berlin '09-'10, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Invitations - Wissenschaftskolleg zu Berlin, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Misc., undated (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Misc., 1989 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Misc., 1993 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Misc., 1996 (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Misc., 1997 (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Misc., 1997 (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Misc., 1998 (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Misc., 1999 (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Misc., 1999 (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Misc., 2000 (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - Misc., 2001 (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - Misc., 2002 (Box 24, Folder 50)
    - Misc., 2003 (Box 24, Folder 51)
    - Misc., 2004 (Box 24, Folder 52)
    - Misc., 2005 (Box 24, Folder 53)
    - Misc., 2005-2006 (Box 24, Folder 54)
    - Misc., 2006 (Box 24, Folder 55)
    - Misc., 2007 (Box 24, Folder 56)
    - Misc., 2008 (Box 24, Folder 57)
    - Misc., 2008 (Box 24, Folder 58)
    - Misc., 2008 (Box 24, Folder 59)
    - Misc., 2010 (Box 24, Folder 60)
    - Misc. correspondence in A-L, 1990-1993 (Box 24, Folder 61)
    - Misc. correspondence in A-L, 1990-1993 (Box 24, Folder 62)
    - Misc. correspondence in A-L, 1990-1993 (Box 24, Folder 63)
    - Misc. correspondence out M-Z, 1990, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 64)
    - Misc. correspondence M-Z, 1984-1993 (Box 24, Folder 65)
    - Misc. correspondence M-Z, 1984-1993 (Box 24, Folder 66)
    - NEH evaluation for Eastern Europe book, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 67)
    - re: NYR, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 68)
    - re: NYR, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 69)
    - re: NYR, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 70)
    - re: NYR, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 71)
    - re: NYR, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 72)
    - re: NYR, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 73)
    - re: NYR, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 74)
    - re: NYR, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 75)
    - re: NYR, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 76)
    - re: NYR, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 77)
    - re: NYR, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 78)
    - re: NYR, 2005-2007 (Box 24, Folder 79)
    - re: NYR, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - re: NYR, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - re: NYR, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - re: NYT, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - re: NYT, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - re: NYT, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - re: NYT, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - re: NYT, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - re: NYT, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - personal - documents, 1978, 1980, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - personal - family misc., 2009, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - publishers gen., 1997, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - publishers gen., 1997 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - publishers gen., 1994-1997 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - re: establishment of Remarque Institute, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - re: establishment of Remarque Institute, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - TJ Thank Yous, 1996-2000 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - TLS, 1996, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - U. of California Press, 1997-1999 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Subseries B: By Correspondent
    - Abrams, Brad, 1996-2008 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Behrent, Michael, 2003, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Beller, Steven, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Birnbaum, Norman, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Boer, Pim den, 2002, undated (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Boswell, Laird, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Brademas, John, 1997-2006 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Bren, Paulina, 1997-2005 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Chirot, Daniel, 1997, undated (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Cohen, Daniel, 1997-2004 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Cohen, Daniel, 1997-2004 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Datta, Venita, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Dombrowski, Nicole, 1997-2006 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Downs, Laura, 1988-1993 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Etmektsoglou, Gabriella, 2002, undated (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Etmektsoglou, Gabriella, 2002, undated (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Etmektsoglou, Gabriella, 1996-1998 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Etmektsoglou, Gabriella, 1996-1998 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Farmer, Sarah, 1997-2000 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Figes, Orlando, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Friguglietti, James, 1993-1999, undated (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Friguglietti, James, 1993-1999, undated (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Frommer, Benjamin, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Furmanski, Phil, 1995-1998 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Gaifman, Hana, 1990, undated (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Gamble, Harry, 1996-2000 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Gechtman, Roni, 1997-2003 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Gechtman, Roni, 1997-2003 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Gechtman, Roni, 1997-2003 (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Geist, Mansouriah, 1999-2009 (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Geist, Mansouriah, 1999-2009 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Geist, Mansouriah, 1999-2009 (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Geist, Mansouriah, 1999-2009 (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - Genest, Isabelle, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - Genest, Isabelle, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - Gier, Jaclyn, 1993-1997 (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - Ginsburg, Paul, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - Goldstein, Cora Sol, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 57)
    - Gress, David, 198-2005 (Box 25, Folder 58)
    - Gross, Irena, 1988-1996 (Box 25, Folder 59)
    - Gross, Irena, 1988-1996 (Box 25, Folder 60)
    - Gross, Jan, 1987-2006 (Box 25, Folder 61)
    - Harris, Ruth, 1992, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 62)
    - Hausman, Tami, 1997-1999 (Box 25, Folder 63)
    - Hausman, Tami, 1997-1999 (Box 25, Folder 64)
    - Heff, Jeffrey, 1992-1999 (Box 25, Folder 65)
    - Heff, Jeffrey, 1992-1999 (Box 25, Folder 66)
    - Hilden, Patricia J., circa 1988 (Box 25, Folder 67)
    - Hockenos, Matthew, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 68)
    - Hogge, Jay, 1991-1996 (Box 25, Folder 69)
    - Hogge, Jay, 1991-1996 (Box 25, Folder 70)
    - Hufton, Olwen, 1996, undated (Box 25, Folder 71)
    - Humphreys, Joshua, 1998-2005 (Box 25, Folder 72)
    - Hunt, Lynne, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 73)
    - Jankowski, Paul, 1992-1998 (Box 25, Folder 74)
    - Jonas, Ray, 1991-1997 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Jonas, Ray, 1991-1997 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Kenney, Padraic, 2000, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Khilnani, Sunil, 1991-1994 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Khilnani, Sunil, 1991-1994 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Kotsonis, Yanni, 1997-2000 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Lagos, Katrina, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Leff, Marni, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Letowski, Ewa, 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Lilla, Mark, 1998, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Livezeanu, Irina, 2000, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Livezeanu, Irina, 2000, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Maguire, Lisa, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Maguire, Lisa, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Maguire, Lisa, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Martin, Jay, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Mazower, Mark, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Mihaies, Mircea, 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Miller, Cecilia, 1994-1997 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Miller, Julia, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Miller, Julia, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Misc. CVs, 1999-2006 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Mitten, Richard, 1999, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Mitten, Richard, undated (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Mitten, Richard, undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Mitten, Richard, 1990, 1998, undated (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Mitten, Richard, undated (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Moyn, Sam, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Müller, Jan, 1998-2003 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Müller, Jan, 1998, undated (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Neiman, Susan, 2005-2006 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Neiman, Susan, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Neiman, Susan, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Ort, Tom, 1997, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Passerini, Louisa, 1993-1997 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Perucic, Jasna, 1990-1999 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Perucic, Jasna, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Prendergast, Christopher, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Pytell, Timothy, 1997-2000 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Rudolph, Nicole, 1998-2005 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Savage, John, circa 2007 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Savage, John, circa 2007 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Savage, John, 1998-2001 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Savage, John, 1999-2006 (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - Savage, John, 1999-2006 (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Schaepdrijver, Sophie de, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - Schaepdrijver, Sophie de, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - Schmidt, Maria, 1989-1999 (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - Schmidt, Maria, 1993-1999 (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - Schneer, Jonathan, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - Seigel, Jerry, 2001, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - Sennett, Richard, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 52)
    - Shore, Marci, 2002-2005 (Box 26, Folder 53)
    - Snyder, Tim, 1997-2006 (Box 26, Folder 54)
    - Snyder, Tim, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 55)
    - Snyder, Tim, 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 56)
    - Snyder, Tim, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 57)
    - Sorina, Galina, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 58)
    - Sorina, Galina, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 59)
    - Standley, Michelle, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 60)
    - Stehlin, Stewart, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 61)
    - Taylor, Lynne, 1990-1993 (Box 26, Folder 62)
    - Taylor, Lynne, undated (Box 26, Folder 63)
    - Temkin, Moshik, 2005-2007 (Box 26, Folder 64)
    - Thompson, Christopher, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 65)
    - Tismaneanu, Vladimir, 1993, 2002-2005 (Box 26, Folder 66)
    - Tismaneanu, Vladimir, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 67)
    - Travis, David, 1989-1993 (Box 26, Folder 68)
    - Utley, Gertje, 1996-1999 (Box 26, Folder 69)
    - Utley, Gertje, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 70)
    - Utley, Gertje, 1997-1999 (Box 26, Folder 71)
    - Vachudova, Milada, 1991-1996 (Box 26, Folder 72)
    - Weiner, Robert I., 1993 (Box 26, Folder 73)
    - Weisberg, Richard, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 74)
    - Wolff, Larry, 2002-2004 (Box 26, Folder 75)
    - Wolin, Richard, 2008 (Box 26, Folder 76)
    - Yu, Mun Ling, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 77)
    - Yu, Mun Ling, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 78)
    - Zipperstein, Steven, 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 79)
    - Zipperstein, Steven, 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 80)
- Series VIII: Press, Interviews, Bulk, 2003-2010; Bulk, 2003-2010 1966-2010
  This series contains articles written about Judt over the course of his career. Some are original clippings, while others are online versions printed out years later. Many are from European news outlets and are not in English.
  - 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - 1988 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - 1991-1994 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - 2001 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - 2002 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - 2003 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - 2003 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - 2004-2005 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - 2006 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - 2006 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - 2006 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - 2006 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - 2006 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - 2006 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - 2007 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - 2008 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - 2009 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - 2009 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - 2010 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - 2010 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Series IX: Multimedia (INTERNAL ONLY)
  This series was pulled together from different parts of the collection, mostly from the Remarque Institute administrative files. Material includes floppy disks of Judt's work, recordings of Remarque Institute Lectures, and assorted CDs and DVDs sent to Judt.
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Administative records are closed for 20 years after their date of creation.
  - Laura MS Backup 2002 (Box 28)
    Technical Access
    Zip drive
  - Backup B '99-'00, 1999-2000 (Box 28)
  - Backup A 2001-2002 Laura (Box 28)
    Zip disk
  - Jair Kessler My Documents & Lotus folder 7/2/98, 1998 (Box 28)
  - Jair MS Back-up 2001/02, 2001-2002 (Box 28)
  - Full Remarque Backup, undated (Box 28)
  - Backup A 2000-01, 2000-2001 (Box 28)
  - Student Backup A 2002, 041202-Ful Tape + Student B (Box 28)
  - Student MS Backup 2002 (Box 28)
  - Backup Jair 2001-2002 (Box 28)
  - Jair Data Backup, undated (Box 28)
  - Backup B 2000-01, 2000-2001 (Box 28)
  - Jair's Files 11/8/96, 1996 (Box 28)
  - Jair Backup A 2002 (Box 28)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 28)
  - Tony, undated (Box 28)
  - Backup Laura 2001-2002 (Box 28)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 28)
  - Backup A 2001-2002 Student (Box 28)
  - Book Reviews, undated (Box 28)
    3.5-inch floppy disk
  - References 2000-2001 (Box 28)
  - Articles, undated (Box 28)
  - Harry Brande Lecture Remarque, undated (Box 28)
  - Remarque + Lucerne 2000-2001 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence + [illegible] 2000-2001 (Box 28)
  - Article + Book referencing, undated (Box 28)
  - Book Reviews, undated (Box 28)
  - Correspondence Rem. Inst., undated (Box 28)
  - CVs + Offers, Misc. + Bibliogs, Business, undated (Box 28)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 28)
  - Lectures/Papers, undated (Box 28)
  - Aron Chapters, undated (Box 28)
  - Judt-Lectures-Papers, undated (Box 28)
  - Aron Folder 2000-2001; Book Reviews 2000-2001; Articles 2000-2001 (Box 28)
  - Student B 2002 (Box 28)
  - Backup B 2001-2002 (Box 28)
  - Jair Back-Up A 2001/02, 2001-2002 (Box 28)
  - Jair Back-Up 1/15/97, 1997 (Box 28)
    Disk case contained note that reads "Back up disk w/ Database to be installed in T.J.'s [illegible]"
  - Tools Disk Do Not Back-Up, undated (Box 28)
  - Jair's Documents '99-'00, 1999-2000 (Box 28)
    Technical Acces
  - Backup Disk B, undated (Box 28)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 28)
  - Backup Student 2001-2002 (Box 28)
  - Remarque Admin PC Backup, undated (Box 28)
  - Laptop back-up 8/29/00, 2000 (Box 28)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 28)
  - Remarque Back-Up Disk A ('99-'00), 1999-2000 (Box 28)
  - Remarque Institute Academic Year 97-98 Back-up, 1997-1998 (Box 28)
  - ABC Radio National-Book Talk-"The Choice Between the Detestable & The Preferable", 2005 (Box 28)
    CD
    Original Location
    Correspondence - professional 2005?
  - La Cabale-A film by Mathieu Verboud, 2008 (Box 28)
    DVD
    Professional Correspondence 2008?
  - Amos Elon ri-res, undated (Box 28)
    Administrative Files - Remarque Lecture - Amos Elon Memorial
  - Amos Elon Memorial Low Quality, undated (Box 28)
  - Remarque Inst., undated (Box 28)
  - "What is Living and What is Dead in Social Democracy," Tony Judt, October 19,2009 (Box 28)
    Administrative Files - Remarque Lecture - Tony Judt
  - "What is Living and What is Dead in Social Democracy," Tony Judt, October 19,2009 (Box 28)
    With note, "Jennifer Ren[?]"
  - "What is Living and What is Dead in Social Democracy," Tony Judt, October 19,2009 (Box 28)
  - Danner Lecture, undated (Box 28)
    Administrative Files - Remarque Lecture - Mark Danner
  - AMS Lecture "America's Edge" 10/23/08, 2008 (Box 28)
    Administrative Files - Remarque Lecture - Anne-Marie Slaughter
  - AMS Lecture "America's Edge" 10/23/08, 2008 (Box 28)
  - America's Edge-Master 10/23/08, 2008 (Box 28)
  - America's Worst Case of Treason, undated (Box 28)
  - Artie Wheeler's Complete Interview, undated (Box 28)